<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open World on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/</link><description>Recent content in Open World on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avalanche</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/avalanche/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/avalanche/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Avalanche is one of the rare 450 RPM Adaptive Frame Machine Guns available exclusively during The Dawning holiday event. Oddly it deals Solar damage instead of Stasis 🙃. Bungie let us know recently that they see MGs as having an add-clear focus, so that&amp;rsquo;s what our rolls will be focusing on.
THE AVALANCHE MACHINE GUN GOD ROLL! (STILL WORTH GETTING?) - Ekeugan * Zephyr is LITERALLY a Stasis Sword - Ehroar I agree with Ekeugan that scope and Masterwork selection don&amp;rsquo;t really matter here; skip stressing too much about these.</description></item><item><title>Berenger's Memory</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/berengers_memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/berengers_memory/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Season 11 is the first time we&amp;rsquo;ve seen Berenger&amp;rsquo;s Memory since Destiny 2 Year 1 (i.e. Season 1). It&amp;rsquo;s the first time it&amp;rsquo;s been available with random rolls. It&amp;rsquo;s a Rapid-Fire Frame with an interesting perk layout that doesn&amp;rsquo;t ultimately result in a lot of super interesting rolls.
PvE Thoughts All of the best perks are in the final column. There are OK perks in the third column but nothing that super synergizes moreso than the other GLs that can roll in this slot.</description></item><item><title>Biting Winds</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/biting_winds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/biting_winds/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
👾 GM Nightfalls (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Elastic String, Tactile String, Agile Bowstring Magazines: Fiberglass Arrow Shaft, Compact Arrow Shaft, Carbon Arrow Shaft Perks 1: Rapid Hit, No Distractions, Surplus Perks 2: Explosive Head Masterworks: Accuracy MW, Reload MW, Draw Time MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Flexible String, Polymer String Magazines: Helical Fletching, Straight Fletching Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Black Scorpion-4sr</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Black Scorpion (now sunset) is Rapid-Fire Frame Scout Rifle in the Energy Slot. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a modern-day Rapid-Fire, check out the Trustee from Deep Stone Crypt.
PvP Thoughts CoolGuy&amp;rsquo;s review (8/2019) is great source of info for the Black Scorpion, as well as the Massive Breakdown Podcast Ep. 148. There are seven perks in the final two columns (versus the usual four to six) and during Season 9, this weapon does not benefit from the Rank 92 extra-final-column-perk bonus.</description></item><item><title>BrayTech Werewolf</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The BrayTech Werewolf is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle first introduced in Season 8 with a fixed roll. It returned in Season 11 and once again returns in the 2021 Festival o the Lost during Season 15.
PvP Thoughts The only competitive AR archetypes right now are the 600s and 720s, so you&amp;rsquo;re gambling on an eventual sandbox change for this to be more effective in PvP.</description></item><item><title>BxR-55 Battler</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/bxr_55_battler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/bxr_55_battler/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The BxR is a new Pulse Rifle available during the 30th Anniversary event that started in December 2021. It has a unique 450 RPM frame, designed as an ode to itself as a Halo weapon. Drewsky and CoolGuy have put together terrific reviews. Drewsky in particular is super excited about the BxR and his coverage of it is some of the best Destiny content creators have to offer: Everything You NEED to Know About Halo&amp;rsquo;s Battle Rifle in Destiny 2.</description></item><item><title>Cold Front</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/cold_front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/cold_front/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
(Rolls have been added, updated and removed based on the changes in the December 2021 Dawning event. The most noticeable difference is the removal/reliance on Surplus which took a huge transitive hit by how much slower abilities are to recharge now.)
Cold Front is a 750 RPM Aggressive Frame (&amp;ldquo;High damage, high recoil&amp;rdquo;) Kinetic Submachine Gun, first introduced long ago during the Season 9 Dawning event.</description></item><item><title>Compass Rose</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/compass_rose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/compass_rose/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Compass Rose is a Precision Frame, Solar shotgun. It was available only during the Season 14 Solstice event.
🧲 Magnetic North (pvp) Classic &amp;ldquo;SnapDraw&amp;rdquo; shotgun roll. Compass Rose can roll with a few Range- increasing barrels in addition to just Full Choke and Rifled, so our odds of picking up these rolls is a bit better.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Rifled Barrel, Full Choke Magazines: Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Quickdraw Perks 2: Snapshot Masterworks: Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Rifled Barrel, Full Choke, Smallbore, Corkscrew Rifling Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Light Mag, Assault Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Crownsplitter</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/crownsplitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/crownsplitter/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Void Aggressive Frame Titan sword. It can do some big smashy damage.
👾 Titan Smash (pve) With the Seasonal Energy Accelerant mod, this can do some big smashy/explody damage.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Jagged Edge Magazines: Heavy Guard Perks 1: Relentless Strikes, Tireless Blade Perks 2: Vorpal, Whirlwind Blade Masterworks: Impact MW Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Dire Promise</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/dire_promise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/world/dire_promise/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Dire Promise is a 140 RPM Hand Cannon that was re-issued all the way back in Season 10 and much has changed. Sunsetting was introduced and then rolled back, 150 RPM HCs were collapsed into the 140 RPM frames and 110 RPMs were upgraded to 120 RPM, turning them into absolute PvP monsters. 140s are middle- of-the-pack but still pack a decent punch.</description></item></channel></rss>