<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iron Banner on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/</link><description>Recent content in Iron Banner on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archon's Thunder</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/archons_thunder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/archons_thunder/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
High-Impact (360 RPM) frame Solar Machine Gun. I don&amp;rsquo;t see this being useful in PvE since it won&amp;rsquo;t be your pick for big DPS or ad clear and relatively situational in PvP.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling, Arrowhead Brake, Fluted Barrel Magazines: Tactical Mag Perks 1: Surplus, Mulligan Perks 2: Rampage Masterworks: Reload MW Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Bite of the Fox</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Bite of the Fox is a Kinetic-slot, Aggressive Frame sniper. It&amp;rsquo;s been in the Iron Banner loot pool since Season 4 and has been re-issued in Season 11. This means if you had a BOTF, it will hit the level cap this season, so you&amp;rsquo;ll want to get a new roll to take you past Season 11.
PvP Thoughts Aggressive Frame snipers are the only ones that can one-shot every super in the Crucible.</description></item><item><title>Crimil's Dagger</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/crimils_dagger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/crimils_dagger/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Crimil&amp;rsquo;s is a 110 RPM Kinetic, Aggressive Frame Hand Cannon that has been re-issued in Season 11 with a higher power cap. It features the same perk pool its always had and since 110s haven&amp;rsquo;t been touched over the years dince Destiny 2&amp;rsquo;s launch, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a pretty limited set of perks we&amp;rsquo;re interested in.
🧲 Magnetic Bullets (pvp) One of the rare weapons that can roll with both Moving Target and Opening Shot at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Finite Impactor</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/finite_impactor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/finite_impactor/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Adaptive Frame (140 RPM) Arc Hand Cannon from Iron Banner. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be very highly rated at the moment for any activity.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Fastdraw HCS, Steadyhand HCS Magazines: Ricochet Rounds Perks 1: Killing Wind, Heating Up Perks 2: Multikill Clip Masterworks: Range MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Truesight HCS, Hitmark HCS Magazines: Extended Mag, Alloy Magazine, Appended Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Fool's Remedy</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/fools_remedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/fools_remedy/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Fool&amp;rsquo;s Remedy is &amp;ldquo;SUROS Rapid-Fire&amp;rdquo; (i.e. fully automatic) 450 RPM Sidearm that has been re-issued in Season 11&amp;rsquo;s Iron Banner. The Remedy is the only SUROS-RF sidearm in the game apart from Dead Man Walking.
If you&amp;rsquo;re going to chase a single weapon from Season 11 Iron Banner (thus far), the Fool&amp;rsquo;s Remedy is the one to go for. People are raving about it because of how it performs at base, its available perks, and that those perks now include the new Iron Banner specific perks: Iron Gaze and Iron Grip.</description></item><item><title>Forge's Pledge</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/forges_pledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/forges_pledge/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Solar Adaptive (390 RPM) frame pulse rifle.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Arrowhead Brake, Chambered Compensator, Corkscrew Rifling Magazines: Tactical Mag, Appended Mag Perks 1: Surplus, Zen Moment Perks 2: Rampage Masterworks: Stability MW, Handling MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Fluted Barrel, Hammer-Forged Rifling Magazines: Accurized Rounds Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Frontier's Cry</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/frontiers_cry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/frontiers_cry/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling Magazines: Tactical Mag Perks 1: Rapid Hit, Adaptive Munitions Perks 2: Kill Clip, Iron Reach Masterworks: Range MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Arrowhead Brake, Corkscrew Rifling, Chambered Compensator, Extended Barrel, Hammer-Forged Rifling Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Appended Mag, Tactical Mag, Flared Magwell Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Occluded Finality</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/occluded_finality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/occluded_finality/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling, Arrowhead Brake, Fluted Barrel Magazines: Extended Mag, Appended Mag Perks 1: Snapshot, Auto-Loading Holster Perks 2: Vorpal Masterworks: Reload MW Variant Chance 1 in ? 👾👾👾🌟 Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition 0.38% 265 👾👾👾 CE (+barrels) 0.</description></item><item><title>Orewing's Maul</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/orewings_maul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/orewings_maul/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Orewing&amp;rsquo;s Maul is a Lightweight Frame, 90RPM Void Grenade Launcher. Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is almost identical to the Truthteller in every way, though it has a materially different (and less excellent) perk pool. Truthteller has more interesting combinations, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean Orewing&amp;rsquo;s can&amp;rsquo;t put in work!
Like Truthteller, Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is part of the &amp;ldquo;Lightweight Frame&amp;rdquo; grenade launchers (breach-loaded, single shot). Lightweight grenade launchers all have a &amp;ldquo;remote detonation&amp;rdquo; ability where they detonate when you release the trigger (or you get a direct hit).</description></item><item><title>Peacebond</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/peacebond/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/ib/peacebond/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Stasis Adaptive (491 RPM) frame sidearm, could be interesting.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling, Fluted Barrel, Hammer-Forged Rifling Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Tactical Mag Perks 1: Subsistence Perks 2: Swashbuckler, Headstone, Demolitionist Masterworks: Range MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Arrowhead Brake, Chambered Compensator Magazines: Appended Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item></channel></rss>