<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S15 - Season of the Lost on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/</link><description>Recent content in S15 - Season of the Lost on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1000 Yard Stare</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/1000_yard_stare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/1000_yard_stare/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
💥 General Purpose (pvp) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Fluted Barrel Magazines: Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Quickdraw, No Distractions Perks 2: Snapshot, Moving Target Masterworks: Handling MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Hammer-Forged Rifling, Corkscrew Rifling Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>A Sudden Death</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/a_sudden_death/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/a_sudden_death/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Arc Aggressive frame shotgun - yet another shotgun in a very crowded slot.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Rifled Barrel Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Assault Mag Perks 1: Slideshot, Surplus Perks 2: One-Two Punch, Frenzy Masterworks: Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Magazines: Tactical Mag, Appended Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>A Swift Verdict</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/a_swift_verdict/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/a_swift_verdict/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Void Precision Frame (260 RPM) sidearm.
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Quickdot SAS, Control SAS Magazines: Ricochet Rounds Perks 1: Full Auto, Surplus Perks 2: Kill Clip Masterworks: Range MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Shortspec SAS, Tactic SAS Magazines: High-Caliber Rounds, Appended Mag, Extended Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Annual Skate</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/annual_skate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/annual_skate/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Solar 140 HC. Good to have, since the last Solar 140 in the game was from Garden. I don&amp;rsquo;t really like the sight and the recoil feels a little strange (I believe it tends left).
☠️ General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Steadyhand HCS, Fastdraw HCS Magazines: Tactical Mag Perks 1: Outlaw, Surplus Perks 2: Timed Payload, Swashbuckler Masterworks: Stability MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Truesight HCS, Hitmark HCS Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Appended Mag, Flared Magwell Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Canis Major</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/canis_major/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/canis_major/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
👾 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Hard Launch, Quick Launch, Volatile Launch, Confined Launch Magazines: Spike Grenades Perks 1: Impulse Amplifier, Clown Cartridge, Field Prep Perks 2: Chain Reaction, Vorpal Masterworks: Velocity MW, Reload MW Variant Chance 1 in ? 👾👾👾🌟 Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition 1.</description></item><item><title>Chrysura Melo</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/chrysura_melo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/chrysura_melo/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
☯️ Murder Brings Harmony (pvp) FrostBolt loves harmony on this gun.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Polygonal Rifling, Smallbore Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Dynamic Sway Reduction, Heating Up Perks 2: Harmony Masterworks: Stability MW, Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Fluted Barrel, Corkscrew Rifling Magazines: Tactical Mag, Flared Magwell Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Contingency Plan</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/contingency_plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/contingency_plan/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Arc VEIST Rapid-Fire (intrinsic full-auto, 260 RPM) scout rifle.
👾 GM Nightfalls (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling, Chambered Compensator, Fluted Barrel Magazines: Appended Mag Perks 1: Surplus Perks 2: Frenzy, One for All Masterworks: Stability MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Arrowhead Brake Magazines: Accurized Rounds, Tactical Mag, Extended Mag Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Darkest Before</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/darkest_before/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/darkest_before/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Arc Rapid-Fire frame pulse.
👾 GM Nightfalls (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Corkscrew Rifling Magazines: Ricochet Rounds, Appended Mag, Extended Mag Perks 1: Overflow, Surplus Perks 2: Full Auto, One for All Masterworks: Stability MW, Reload MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Arrowhead Brake, Chambered Compensator, Fluted Barrel Magazines: High-Caliber Rounds Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>Fractethyst</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/fractethyst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/fractethyst/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Fractethyst is a Precision Frame (65 RPM) Stasis Shotgun, introduced in Season 15. The best roundup I&amp;rsquo;ve seen is courtesy of Castle Content, and much of what you&amp;rsquo;ll see here is recapped from his review.
PvP Thoughts Finally a replacement for the fallen king of Destiny Shotguns Dust Rock Blues! Fractethyst will round out your Kinetic slot shotgun suite and will do it in style, with some super interesting new perks.</description></item><item><title>Half-Truths</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/half_truths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/half_truths/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
&amp;hellip;
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
💥 General Purpose (pve) &amp;hellip;
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll Barrels: Jagged Edge Magazines: Swordmaster's Guard Perks 1: Tireless Blade, Relentless Strikes, Duelist's Trance Perks 2: Eager Edge, Assassin's Blade Masterworks: Impact MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below) Barrels: Honed Edge, Tempered Edge, Hungry Edge Magazines: Enduring Guard, Heavy Guard, Balanced Guard Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item></channel></rss>